ABOUT ME

Motivated, I love my work,cooperative,working in teams, leading, responsible And I am seeking to be one of the effective people in my position. I have programming for more than five years and I done many applications. I am interested in web development.

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

ARABIC

LINKS

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hisha m-hamdoon-b44685197?jobid=...

DRIVING LICENSE

Driving license category Specially

HISHAM

JUNIOR BACKEND DEVELOPER





hamdon_22@hotmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

BUSINESS CITY CO, LTD

Riyadh

May 2022 - Present

Junior Dotnet developer

Participate in requirements analysis

Collaborate with internal teams to produce software design and architecture

Test and deploy applications and systems

Revise, update, refactor and debug code

Improve existing software

Serve as an expert on applications and provide technical support Participate, develope APIs

BUSINESS CITY CO, LTD

Rivadh

Oct 2022 - Present

Technical Support Engineer

I work as technical support engineer on deploying the systems on company's test and production servers then test it. deploying system on the clients servers.

training them on how to use the systems as end users, get their notes and additional requirements about the systems. integrate the system with other client's resources such as HR system.

FINANCIAL & **BANKING SYSTEMS COMPANY**

Khartoum, Sudan Oct 2019 - Dec 2020

ZAIN SUDAN

Khartoum, Sudan Apr 2019 - Aug 2019

Software Developer

I am working as a trainee on some changes and enhancements on the major system of company.

Customer Care Agent

Receiving customers complaints and fix it directly or make a complaint for other department based on the type of problem.

EDUCATION

AL ZAIEM AL AZHARY UNIVERSITY

2018

SQL PROGRAMMING AND MYSQL **DEVELOPER CERTIFICATION TRAINING** 2021

UDEMY 2023

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

COURSE, Data Modeling/Warehousing and Database Administration

I learnt sql command DDL,DML,DML,making views,joining tables, stored procedure, cursors...etc using RDBMS MySQL database.

Diploma

I learnt Complete guide to ASP .Net Core Framework online on Udemy Platform and I got the certificate on february 2023. I learnt MVC architecture.

N-Tier architecture.

Razor pages.

Repository Pattern.

Integrate Payment API (Stripe).

Identity in .Net

Entity framwork and how its working with database I learnt how to make a complete MVC project. and much more in ASP. Net Core framework

SKILLS

HYPERTEXT MARKUP LANGUAGE (HTML) E-COMMERCE PYTHON (PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE) INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY DJANGO (WEB FRAMEWORK) SQL PHP C# SOL SERVER

PROBLEMS SOLVING